ALEKSANDRA KIELESINSKA

MOTION DESIGNER/XR DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Motion designer with experience in developing immersive experience. Working for clients such as Disney, and Financial Times. Always keen to challenge and pushing the boundaries while exploring newest technology, with passion for film and art.

kieleax@gmail.com +44 7727 120534 London,UK

LINKS

Portfolio:

axkiele.com

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/axkielesinska

EDUCATION

MA Virtual & Augmented Reality Goldsmiths University of London 2021-2022

VR/AR Applications development. 3D Graphics and User Experience. Gaining experience in developing XR applications in Unity using C#. Learning about psychological aspect of using Extended Reality.

Bsc Visual Effects (VFX) with Animation De Montfort University 2018-2021

1st Year: Film Production I Storytelling I 3D modeling I Compositing 2nd Year: Tracking, Rigging and compositing I Modeling and Animation I Video and Imaging Techniques. 3rd Year: Match moving and Mo-cap I Postproduction for video and film I Set design for VFX and Game Environment.

A-Levels Equivalent, Collage of Art Collage of Art Kielce, Poland 2013- 2017

Studying core collage subjects as well as art focus subjects such as history of art sculpting, advanced drawing classes, concept art, media production and design.

SKILLS

Languages: C# | C++ | JavaScript | Visual Scripting

Platform: Windows I Mac

Software: Unity | Unreal | Maya | After Effects | Cinema 4D (Redshift) | Da Vinci | Premiere Pro | Studio Lens | Spark AR | InDesign | Illustrator | Figma

WORK EXPERIENCE

Motion Designer Financial Times Live

Oct 2022 - now

Developing digital assets for FT Live events, video post-production, 2D and 3D motion graphics for branding videos and marketing campaigns. Designing digital and print content for high-profile events. Producing engaging visual content that resonates with diverse audiences, contributing to the success of numerous events.

Creative designer (freelance) The Walt Disney Company

Apr 2022 - now

Designing and producing motion graphics and GFX for marketing sizzle videos, as well as social media reels and posts. Creating graphics and illustrations for several Disney campaigns, ensuring that the content is visually compelling and aligns with the brand's messaging. In addition, video editing and post-production.

Graphic Designer/Illustrator Pattern Atelier

Nov 2021 - May 2022

Creating high-quality illustrations and graphics. Creating captivating product photo shoots and mocaps that showcase products in a unique and compelling way. Setting up print-ready files and distribution of marketing and promotional materials. Creating and managing social media content, helping to build brand awareness and engage with audiences. Using industry-standard software such as Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, and InDesign

Freelance Rigger/Animator

Feb 2021 - Nov 2021

Handling the complete rigging pipeline, including creating rigs for primary characters, quadrupeds, and birds. Developing highly detailed and precise 3D loop cycle animations. Using industry-standard software such as Maya, Blender, and Unity to create visually compelling and highly realistic characters and creatures, contributing to successful projects

Graphic Designer (Internship)
Matin Prime

Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

Creating graphics, illustrations, and advertising banners for various clients. Designing for print, I also honed my skills in web design, creating visually appealing and user-friendly layouts for various digital platforms. I assisted with the development of website elements, including icons, logos, and other design features.